http://www.1010data.com/privacy-policy/

Last Updated December 2, 2020
This Privacy Notice (the “Notice”) is intended to describe how 1010data, Inc. and its affiliates (“1010data”, “we”, “us” or “our”) our practices regarding information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular individual (collectively “Personal Information”) collected and received through our websites (“Sites”) and big data products and services (“Services”).
I. Scope of this Notice
This Notice applies only to information collected and received by us through access and use of the Services and/or Sites and does not apply to any other information collected by us through other means. Further, this Notice does not cover the activities of third parties.
It is your responsibility to read and understand this Notice. If you do not agree to the practices described in this Notice and do not wish to be bound by it, you should not use our Services or Sites
This Notice explains the following:
• What personal information we collect and receive• How we use Personal Information• How we disclose Personal Information• How we secure and store Personal Information• Choices about receiving marketing messages• Cookies and “do not track”• Other websites• California privacy rights• Access to and accuracy of Personal Information• Users in the European Economic Area (EEA) and Switzerland• How to contact us.
II. What Personal Information We Collect and Receive
The Personal Information we collect and receive may include the following:
Personal information you provide when you register with our Services (including for trial access), request information from us and when we perform work for you. These identifiers and professional or employment-related information may include: your name, industry, organization name, job, contact information, such as e-mail address, phone number, and shipping address, payment information, such as a credit or debit card number, and password for your account access.
• Personal information that you upload into our Services.• Personal Information related to transactions requested or completed through the Sites.• Personal Information you provide to us in the “Careers” section of the Sites when you submit an application for an open position. These identifiers and professional or employment-related information may include: name, email, phone, resume, cover letter, LinkedIn profile, work authorization status, location (commuting status), academic status (for interns), reference, and base salary expectations.• Communications with us (whether in writing, by email, or by telephone).
Moreover, whenever you visit the Sites or use our Services, we also receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your computer or mobile device’s operating system type and version, device identification number, browser type and language, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, and geographic areas derived from your IP address, our cookie information, file information, time stamped logs regarding access times and duration of visits, the websites you visited before coming to the Sites, and other internet activity information relating to your activities on our Sites, including the pages you request (collectively “Automatically Collected Data”). Alone or in combination with other information, Automatically Collected Data may constitute Personal Information.
III. How we use Personal Information
We use Personal Information collected through our Sites or through use of our Services for the following purposes:
• Provide and deliver you access to our Services after you’ve registered, paid for, or requested such access.• Provide software updates and communicate with you about our Services;• Operate and improve our internal operations, systems, products, Sites and Services;• Understand you and your preferences and to enhance your experience;• Respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;• Communicate with you about promotions, upcoming events, and news about our Services;• For human resources management;• Link or combine information about you with other Personal Information we get from third parties, to help understand our users’ needs and provide our users with better and more personalized service;• Enforce our terms and conditions or protect our business, third party service providers, or users; and • Protect against, investigate, and deter fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.
We may also contact you about your registration details, to manage any account or subscription you have with us, or to provide customer service, even if you have opted-out of or declined to consent to receiving promotional emails. We may also contact you to inform you of revisions to this Notice.
We also may use Automatically Collected Data to improve our Services or Sites and occasionally for other purposes that are compatible with the purposes described above.
IV. The Sources of Personal Information
We collect Personal Information from the following categories of sources:
• You: When you voluntarily provide Personal Information to us;• Software: Information automatically collected via cookies, web logs, web beacons, and other software-based analytics tools; and• Commercial partners: Information obtained from our data licensors and commercial partners, including commercial data aggregators.
V. How We Disclose Personal Information
In the past 12 months we have disclosed the following categories of Personal Information with the following categories of third parties for business purposes:
Category of Personal Information
Category of Third Party
Identifiers or professional information
Our affiliates (such as subsidiaries that we own).
Service providers: We use service providers such as data storage and data analysis companies and marketing technology companies. Such service providers can only use Personal Information to provide such services to us and for no other purpose.
Parties to a corporate transaction or proceeding: In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, bankruptcy, dissolution or similar event, Personal Information may be part of the transferred assets.
Public authorities and legal proceedings: We may disclose Personal Information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as required by law, and disclose and use such information as we believe necessary or appropriate to (a) comply with applicable laws and lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities; (b) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Sites and/or the Services; (c) protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others; and (d) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity.
Professional or employment-related information
Our affiliates (such as subsidiaries that we own).Service providers: We use service providers such as human resources technology vendors. Such service providers can only use Personal Information to provide such services to us and for no other purpose.
Parties to a corporate transaction or proceeding: In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, bankruptcy, dissolution or similar event, Personal Information may be part of the transferred assets.
Public authorities and legal proceedings: We may disclose Personal Information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as required by law, and disclose and use such information as we believe necessary or appropriate to (a) comply with applicable laws and lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities; (b) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Sites and/or the Services; (c) protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others; and (d) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity.
Internet activity information
Service providers: We use service providers such as data storage and data analysis companies and marketing technology companies. Such service providers can only use Personal Information to provide such services to us and for no other purpose.
Certain third parties, including analytics companies, advertisers and ad networks, may also automatically collect information about you through our Sites, using cookies, Web beacons, device identifiers, and similar technologies, including personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites, devices, online channels and applications.
VI. Do Not Track (‘DNT’) Settings
California law requires us to let you know how we respond to web browser Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals. Because there currently isn’t an industry or legal standard for recognizing or honoring DNT signals, we don’t respond to them at this time.
VII. California Privacy Rights
a) Introduction
If you are a California resident you may also have the right:
• To request disclosure of the categories and specific pieces of Personal Information collected about you; • To request the disclosure of the business purpose for collecting or selling Personal Information; the categories of third parties with whom it is shared, and the categories of sources from which Personal Information is collected; • To request the deletion of Personal Information, subject to the limitations set forth in California Civil Code Section 1798.105(d); • not to be discriminated against for exercising the rights guaranteed by California Civil Code Section 1798.100 et seq.
For a list of categories of Personal Information collected and the purposes for the processing of that Personal Information, please refer to Section II above.
b) Requests to Know
You have the right to request that we disclose:
• The categories of Personal Information we collect; • The categories of Personal Information we have sold or disclosed for a business purpose; • The categories of sources from which we collect Personal Information about you; • Our business or commercial purpose for selling or collecting Personal Information;
The categories of Personal Information sold or shared about you, as well as the categories of third parties to whom the Personal Information was sold, by category of Personal Information for each party to whom information was sold;
The specific pieces of Personal Information collected about you.
Delivery may take place electronically or by mail. We are not required to respond to requests relating to Personal Information more than twice in a 12-month period.
c) Requests to Delete
With certain exceptions, you have the right to request that we delete any Personal Information we have collected about you. Upon receiving a verified request to delete Personal Information about you, we will do so unless otherwise authorized by law.
d) Verifiable Requests
We will acknowledge the receipt of requests to know or requests to delete Personal Information free of charge, within 10 business days. In order to protect your privacy and the security of Personal Information, we may verify your request by asking you to provide additional Personal Information for us to verify your identity. We will respond to your request within 45 calendar days of receipt, provided that we have been able to successfully verify your identity.
You may submit a request to know or a request to delete Personal Information via email at privacy@1010data.com.
e) Sale of Personal Information
In the last 12 months, we have not sold Personal Information collected in and through the Sites or the Services. Consequently, we do not have a Do Not Sell My Info-functionality on the Sites.
f) The Right to Non-Discrimination
You have a right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of your California privacy rights.
g) Authorized Agents
You may designate an authorized agent to make requests on your behalf. You must provide an authorized agent written permission to submit a request on your behalf, and we may require that you verify your identity directly with us. Alternatively, an authorized agent that has been provided power of attorney pursuant to Probate Code sections 4000-4465 may submit a request on your behalf.
VIII. How Do We Use Cookies?
Some of the features on the Sites require the use of "cookies" - small text files that are stored on your device's hard drive. We use cookies to measure which pages are being accessed, and which features are most frequently used. This enables us to continuously improve the Sites to meet the needs of our visitors.
The following sets out how we may use different categories of cookies and your options for managing cookie settings:
Type of Cookies
Description
Managing Settings
Required cookies
Required cookies enable you to navigate the Sites and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Sites and using our services. If you have chosen to identify yourself to us, we use cookies containing encrypted information to allow us to uniquely identify you. These cookies allow us to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the Site and to process your online transactions and requests.
Because required cookies are essential to operate the Sites, there is no option to opt out of these cookies.
Performance cookies
These cookies collect information about how you use the Sites. including which pages you go to most often and if they receive error messages from certain pages. These cookies do not collect information that individually identifies you. Information is only used to improve how the Site functions and performs. From time to time, we may engage third parties to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information relating to individuals who visit the Sites. We may also utilize Flash cookies for these purposes.
To learn how to opt out of performance cookies using your browser settings, click here. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, click here.
Functionality cookies
Functionality cookies allow the Sites to remember information you have entered or choices you make (such as your username, language, or your region) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies also enable you to optimize your use of the Sites after logging in. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. We may use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on the Site to personalize your visit.
To learn how to opt out of functionality cookies using your browser settings, click here. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, click here.
Targeting or Advertising cookies
From time-to-time, we may engage third parties to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from individuals who visit the Sites. We sometimes use cookies delivered by third parties to track the performance of our advertisements. For example, these cookies remember which browsers have visited the Sites. By way of example, as you browse the Sites, advertising cookies may be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our advertising partners then enable us to present you with retargeted advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with the Sites. Third parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on the Sites or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.
To learn more about these and other advertising networks and their opt out instructions, click here. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, click here.
IX. For Residents of the European Economic Area (EEA)
(a) Legal Basis For Processing Personal Information
The legal bases for our processing of Personal Information about you are as follows:
• Contract: When you purchase Services from us, we collect Personal Information about you that is necessary for completing that transaction and delivering the Services to you; • Consent: We may obtain your consent to collect Personal Information for distinct purposes such as receiving marketing communications from us. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time; and • Legitimate Interest: We have a legitimate interest to collect Personal Information about you for certain purposes such as data analytics and the protection and administration of the Sites and the Services so that we can (i) understand our customers’ preferences and improve the features available on the Sites and the Services; (ii) to protect the Sites from information security threats and 1010data in connection with legal claims and proceedings; (iii) to communicate administrative changes in connection with the use of the Sites and the Services; and (iv) to comply with laws that apply to us and the Sites and/or the Services.
(b) Transfers of Personal Information1010data is based in the United States of America. If you are located in the EEA or Switzerland, this means that we may transfer Personal Information outside of the EEA or Switzerland. Such transfers are made using adequate safeguards, such as the EU Standard Contractual Clauses for Controller-to-Controller and Controller-to-Processor Transfers.
(c) Your Rights
You have the following rights with respect to the Personal Information we hold about you:
• The right to know what Personal Information we hold about you; • The right to have incomplete, incorrect, outdated, or unnecessary Personal Information corrected, deleted, or updated; • The right to request that we restrict the processing of Personal Information we hold about you in certain circumstances; • The right to object to the processing of Personal Information we hold about you; and/or • The right to receive any Personal Information we hold about you in a structured and commonly used machine-readable format or have such Personal Information transmitted to another company.
In connection with exercising your rights described above, we may request additional Personal Information for purposes of verifying your identity and for no other purpose.
Depending on where you live, you may have a right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority or other regulatory agency if you believe that we have violated any of the rights concerning Personal Information about you. We encourage you to first reach out to us at privacy@1010data.com so we have an opportunity to address your concerns directly before you do so.
To exercise any of the rights described above, please contact privacy@1010data.com. We seek to promptly respond to your inquiry.
X. Choices About Receiving Marketing Messages
When you register or respond to one of our communications or offers, we may ask you to make choices about receiving further marketing communications from us. In addition, should you wish to stop receiving marketing communications directly from us, you will be able to unsubscribe or opt-out, or you can contact us as described at the end of this Notice and we will make the changes for you. Please remember to include your full name and email address in order that we may make the changes that you request. To opt out of communications provided by third parties, you may need to opt out or change your privacy settings with the third party. For example, if you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from us through your social media account, you can modify your privacy settings for your social media account to change or limit the information shared.
XI. Security
We take reasonable and appropriate measures to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Information. Despite our efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee the security of Personal Information during its transmission or its storage on our systems. Further, while we attempt to ensure the integrity and security of Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent malicious third-parties from illegally obtaining access to Personal Information. We do not warrant or represent that Personal Information about you will be protected against, loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties.
XII. Changes to This Notice
This Notice may change from time to time, effective from the date mentioned in the updated version of the Notice. You can tell when this Notice was last updated by reviewing the Last Updated legend at the top of this page. Please check the Sites periodically to review such changes in the Notice.
XIII. Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Notice or about our privacy or data security practices, please contact us via the following:
privacy@1010data.com or via mail:
1010data, Inc.750 Third Avenue Fourth FloorNew York, NY 10017
Let’s Talk
Smarter decisions. Better outcomes.
750 Third Avenue, 4th Floor New York, NY 10017 USAContact Us
Phone: +1 212-405-1010
Legal Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
